<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Protective the eye to prevent myopia is of vital importance</title>
    <link href="/2021/03/16/Protective-the-eye-to-prevent-myopia-is-of-vital-importance/"/>
    <url>/2021/03/16/Protective-the-eye-to-prevent-myopia-is-of-vital-importance/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I still remember that only 4 of the more than 50 classmates in the high school class did not wear glasses, and now almost everyone around me has myopia. In retrospect, when I was about at the sixth grade of elementary school. I firmly believed that it looked cool to wear glasses, therefore, I deliberately developed a bad habit of using my eyes in an unhealthy way. When I had a slight tendency towards myopia, my parents had already taken me to see the doctor, hoping to control pseudomyopia. Now I really regret it! Once myopia occurs, it is irreversible. Compared with correction and treatment, prevention is the key.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-46.png"></p><p>According to a survey on the rising rates of myopia and high myopia around the world published by on scientific journal Ophthalmology of the American Academy of Ophthalmology, by 2050, 4.76 billion people will have myopia (which accounts for 49.8% of the world’s population); 0.938  billion people suffer from high myopia (which accounta for 9.8% of the world’s population). In other words, by 2050, more than 50% of the world’s population will have myopia. The prevention and control of myopia is already an issue that should be paid attention to by the whole world.</p><h5 id="Everyone-may-have-the-gene-of-myopia"><a href="#Everyone-may-have-the-gene-of-myopia" class="headerlink" title="Everyone may have the gene of myopia"></a>Everyone may have the gene of myopia</h5><p><img src="/images/pasted-47.png"></p><p>There are many rumors about the inheritance of myopia: some say that it will be inherited, some say that it will not be inherited; some say that it is inherited only after 600 degrees… In fact, they are not all true. Myopia is indeed related to inheritance, but what a child inherits is a constitution that is prone to myopia, instead of myopia itself.</p><p>Therefore, prevention of myopia should start from the parents. If both parents have myopia,they should indeed keep alert, but acquired factors should also be taken into consideration.</p><h5 id="“Staying-in-the-house”-makes-more-and-more-people-to-develop-myopia"><a href="#“Staying-in-the-house”-makes-more-and-more-people-to-develop-myopia" class="headerlink" title="“Staying in the house” makes more and more people to develop myopia"></a>“Staying in the house” makes more and more people to develop myopia</h5><p><img src="/images/pasted-48.png"></p><p>Seeing objects in a close distance plays an important role in developing myopia, but it is not the only factor. It is generally believed that reading a book or playing mobile phone keeps our eyes focused on a close range for a long time, making us lose sight over time, which is probably the most deeply rooted cause of myopia.</p><p>Indeed, a large number of studies have found that there is a significant correlation between using eyes in a short distance and myopia, and the prevalence of myopia is often higher in areas with higher universal education.</p><h5 id="Less-outdoor-activities-have-a-significant-correlation-with-the-occurrence-of-myopia"><a href="#Less-outdoor-activities-have-a-significant-correlation-with-the-occurrence-of-myopia" class="headerlink" title="Less outdoor activities have a significant correlation with the occurrence of myopia"></a>Less outdoor activities have a significant correlation with the occurrence of myopia</h5><p><img src="/images/pasted-49.png"></p><p>At present, more and more studies have confirmed that the increase in outdoor activities under strong light in childhood can significantly reduce the risk of myopia and delay the development of myopia to a certain extent.<br>src=http___5b0988e595225.cdn.sohucs.com_q_70,c_zoom,w_640_ima</p><p>Outdoor activities cover a wide range, including walking outdoors, playing, having a picnic, and even reading, etc.<br>Australian scholars have conducted a three-year follow-up study on more than 4,000 primary and secondary school students, and reached the conclusion: You can effectively prevent myopia as long as you spend enough time outdoors, whether you are exercising or not. It is believed by the academic community that this may be because outdoor light has an impact on the development of the eye’s refractive system.</p><h5 id="Don’t-think-that-myopia-can-be-solved-by-simply-wearing-an-extra-pair-of-glasses"><a href="#Don’t-think-that-myopia-can-be-solved-by-simply-wearing-an-extra-pair-of-glasses" class="headerlink" title="Don’t think that myopia can be solved by simply wearing an extra pair of glasses."></a>Don’t think that myopia can be solved by simply wearing an extra pair of glasses.</h5><p>Generally speaking, the higher the degree of myopia, the higher the risk of blinding diseases such as retinal detachment, and the worse the quality of life in the future, it is imperative to prevent and control myopia.</p><p>For children, as long as they use their eyes scientifically, carry out more outdoor activities, and have a reasonable diet and ensure adequate sleep, myopia can still be prevented or controlled to a large extent.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>March</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>In face of Contraception</title>
    <link href="/2021/03/09/In-face-of-Contraception/"/>
    <url>/2021/03/09/In-face-of-Contraception/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Every adult, sooner or later, will inevitably come into contact with sex, and we are destined to deal with contraception. Before having a clear plan to have a baby, please spare no efforts to take contraception seriously.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-40.png"></p><p>Perhaps because I have heard many examples living in a doctor’s family, I believe teenagers are lack of sex education. Biology courses teach where babies come from, but contraception is always a topic that people don’t want to mention. Even some married adults don’t know enough recognition of correct contraception.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-41.png"></p><p>Today, let’s talk about common contraception methods. Are they really useful? Which is better?</p><h4 id="Unreliable-contraception-methods"><a href="#Unreliable-contraception-methods" class="headerlink" title="Unreliable contraception methods"></a>Unreliable contraception methods</h4><p>Due to the lack of sex education, human beings have various “unconventional methods” based on physiological laws or word of mouth. However, the actual effect is bad. These seemingly reasonable contraceptive methods are actually a kind of gambling.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-42.png"></p><blockquote></blockquote><ol><li>Unprotected sex during lactation<br>Ovulation can’t be prevented for 100% during lactation. Some women judge whether to ovulate by whether they resume menstruation after giving birth. In fact, most woman ovulate before they resume menstruation.</li><li>Contraception in safe period<br>Sperm can survive in a woman’s body for up to 5 days, and a woman’s ovulation period is also affected by various factors. Therefore, it is quite unreliable to carry out contraception in safe period. </li><li>In vitro ejaculation<br>Before ejaculation, the fluid secreted by men contains sperm, in addition, this may lead to functional non-ejaculation syndrome.</li></ol><h4 id="Reliable-methods-of-contraception"><a href="#Reliable-methods-of-contraception" class="headerlink" title="Reliable methods of contraception"></a>Reliable methods of contraception</h4><p><img src="/images/pasted-43.png"></p><h6 id="1-Take-medicine"><a href="#1-Take-medicine" class="headerlink" title="1.Take medicine"></a>1.Take medicine</h6><p>Regulate estrogen and progesterone, make the body believe that it has become pregnant, thus suspend ovulation. Common medicine includes: contraceptive pills, contraceptive implants under the skin(99.95% success rate).</p><p>Short-term contraceptives (99.7% success rate) VS emergency contraceptives (80% success rate)</p><h6 id="The-application-situation-is-different"><a href="#The-application-situation-is-different" class="headerlink" title="The application situation is different:"></a>The application situation is different:</h6><p>short-term contraceptives can be used for a long time, usually the oral medicine-taking time is 21 days of each menstrual cycle, suitable for ordinary women in childbearing age.</p><p>Emergency contraceptives cannot be taken frequently. They are usually taken orally after sex life, with the time being within 72 hours. It is suitable for women who have suffered accidental injuries or have sex without protection.</p><h6 id="The-mechanism-of-action-is-different"><a href="#The-mechanism-of-action-is-different" class="headerlink" title="The mechanism of action is different:"></a>The mechanism of action is different:</h6><p>the progesterone in short-term contraceptives is very close to human progesterone, which can not only terminate pregnancy, but also help prevent female diseases, such as ovarian cancer, endometrial cancer, etc. and it is of certain effect on regulating female hormone levels.</p><p>However, the emergency contraceptive pill is only a remedy after having sex, which will change the women’s menstrual cycle, leading to female endocrine disorders, therefore, it has high risk of failure, and obvious side effects, and can only be used for emergency.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-44.png"></p><h6 id="2-Tools"><a href="#2-Tools" class="headerlink" title="2.Tools"></a>2.Tools</h6><p>Prevent the sperm from meeting the egg, or prevent the fertilized egg from implanting and developing. Common tools include: condoms(98% success rate), intrauterine devices(99.8% success rate).</p><h6 id="3-Surgical-methods"><a href="#3-Surgical-methods" class="headerlink" title="3.Surgical methods"></a>3.Surgical methods</h6><p><img src="/images/pasted-45.png"></p><p>Use surgery to close the vas deferens/fallopian tube to prevent the release of sperm or eggs.  Common surgeries include: Fallopian tube(99% success rate) / vas deferens ligation surgery(99.9% success rate).</p><p>Of course, no matter which contraceptive method you choose, it must be based on actual physical conditions of both partners. There is no best, only the most suitable. Finally, I want to remind everyone that, except for condoms, no method of contraception can prevent sexually transmitted diseases.</p><p>***Data of “success rate” mentioned in the paper originates from UTD **</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>March</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Physical examination is necessary</title>
    <link href="/2021/03/02/Physical-examination-is-necessary/"/>
    <url>/2021/03/02/Physical-examination-is-necessary/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>At the beginning and the end of the year, major medical examination institutions reached the peak. As modern people pay more and more attention to health, more and more people are afraid of facing the results of the medical examination form and rejecting the medical examination for fear of finding problems. In fact, a physical examination is really necessary for maintaining health.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-33.png"></p><p>Through physical examination, one can understand one’s own health state and discover some early diseases that are not easy to detect, so as to prevent and stop the development of the disease in time. However, for physical examination, it’s not enough to only do examinations, they should also know how to do it.</p><h3 id="What-items-should-be-checked-in-the-physical-examination-for-different-age-groups"><a href="#What-items-should-be-checked-in-the-physical-examination-for-different-age-groups" class="headerlink" title="What items should be checked in the physical examination for different age groups?"></a>What items should be checked in the physical examination for different age groups?</h3><p><img src="/images/pasted-34.png"></p><p>Many physical examinations are often based on a package. Both the 20-year-old boy and the 50-year-old uncle receive the same package.<br>Different physical examinations should be adopted for different person，and it should be choosen according to their age, gender, occupation, health status, and family medical history, etc., which is carried out from a comprehensive consideration.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-35.png"></p><h3 id="How-often-should-people-carry-out-physical-examination"><a href="#How-often-should-people-carry-out-physical-examination" class="headerlink" title="How often should people carry out physical examination?"></a>How often should people carry out physical examination?</h3><p><img src="/images/pasted-36.png"></p><p>According to recommendations of the World Health Organization:<br>Under 45 years old, a health checkup will be carried out every one to two years;<br>People aged 45 and above should carry out a health check at least once a year;<br>People with health problems should undergo one or more physical examinations per year for corresponding health problems;<br>Women who have sex life should receive a gynecological examination every year.</p><h3 id="Based-on-family-history-and-personal-medical-history"><a href="#Based-on-family-history-and-personal-medical-history" class="headerlink" title="Based on family history and personal medical history"></a>Based on family history and personal medical history</h3><p><img src="/images/pasted-37.png"></p><p>Certain diseases with obvious family clusters, such as diabetes, stroke, coronary heart disease, breast cancer, colon cancer and so on. If there is a clear history of a certain disease in the family, physical examination items related to it should be added.</p><p>At present, scientific health management should be carried out in the medical examination industry, subsequently, the results of the physical examination should be integrated into the health management steps, so that people can enjoy a more comprehensive and systematic service, and can directly seeek medical consultation from the preventive examination when a disease problem is detected, so as to eliminate complicated processes and save more time for people.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-38.png"></p><p>Last but not least, health and life can’t be brought by money. As we grow old, the chances of humans suffering from certain diseases increase. Most of these diseases have no obvious symptoms in the early stage, but often have serious consequences. If you can perform regular health checks on their body, discover diseases in time, and treat them before it becomes serious, then the probability of various of diseases will be greatly reduced. A health checkup is of great significance.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>March</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Nearly perfect myopia surgery</title>
    <link href="/2021/02/16/Nearly-perfect-myopia-surgery/"/>
    <url>/2021/02/16/Nearly-perfect-myopia-surgery/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I finally took off my eye glasses!  This is the first comment I made after undergoing full femtosecond refractive surgery three years ago. Fortunately, my vision has maintained the postoperative level for three years without any adverse reactions.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-19.png"></p><p>Before deciding to undergo refractive surgery, my father and I compared differences of various of surgical options, and also saw many postoperative cases on the Internet. At that time, I wanted to remove the glasses, but I could only see the experience sharing of “success” and “no regrets”. I think those who have “sequelae” are unlucky, which I will definitely not encounter.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-20.png"></p><p>However, in retrospect, everyone did mention a lot of valuable information, but I selectively ignored it.  Based on my experience, I still think that myopia laser surgery is very close to perfect in existing surgeries.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-21.png"></p><p>When it comes to the operation process, there is probably a negative pressure ring that fixes the eyes to prevent the eyeballs from turning randomly, and then the button is activated，after the doctor operates for tens of seconds, and the operation will be over，which is easy and efficient.  After I successfully removed the eye glasses, many of my friends wanted to try it, either, but not everyone can do myopia surgery.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-22.png"></p><p>No surgery is 100% safe，there may also be many contraindications, such as some diseases related to the eye and systemic diseases.  Whether the surgery can be carried out or what kind of surgery can be carried out depends on the preoperative examination and the doctor’s judgment. For example, my roommate could not accept the operation because of trichiasis, then why I say that this operation is almost perfect?</p><h3 id="Laser-surgery-can-meet-the-needs-of-most-people"><a href="#Laser-surgery-can-meet-the-needs-of-most-people" class="headerlink" title="Laser surgery can meet the needs of most people"></a>Laser surgery can meet the needs of most people</h3><p><img src="/images/pasted-23.png"></p><p>Simply speaking, laser myopia surgery can thin the cornea. The higher the myopia degree, the thicker the cornea that needs to be cut. In terms of surgery method, a principle that suits most people is:</p><ol><li>When there is sufficient corneal thickness, the degree and other conditions are also suitable, half femtosecond or full femtosecond is preferred</li><li>If the corneal thickness is insufficient and the patient is of moderate to low level of myopia, then surface surgery such as t-PRK can be given priority.</li><li>In recent years, lens implantation (ICL) has gradually become mainstream.</li></ol><h3 id="Safe-operation-process"><a href="#Safe-operation-process" class="headerlink" title="Safe operation process"></a>Safe operation process</h3><p>Laser surgery for myopia is a highly programmed ultra-fast operation. Unexpected results rarely occur during and after the operation, and there is almost no opportunity for doctors to make mistakes.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-24.png"></p><h3 id="Less-adverse-reactions-after-the-surgery"><a href="#Less-adverse-reactions-after-the-surgery" class="headerlink" title="Less adverse reactions after the surgery"></a>Less adverse reactions after the surgery</h3><p>With technological innovation, the incidence of many common postoperative complications (dry eye syndrome, poor wound healing) has also been greatly reduced.  But after experiencing many “unsatisfied” cases, I hope that everyone will weigh this operation in a comprehensive way. A reasonable psychological expectation is a necessary prerequisite.</p><p>Im brief, myopia surgery is a choice after fully weighing risks and benefits，hope that the development of science and technology will bring us closer and closer to a safer and perfect operation.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>February</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Quitting smoking can only be achieved by persistence</title>
    <link href="/2021/02/09/Quitting-smoking-can-only-be-achieved-by-persistence/"/>
    <url>/2021/02/09/Quitting-smoking-can-only-be-achieved-by-persistence/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When it comes to smoking and the prevention of lung cancer, I always think of a terrifying experience. Once upon a time, I went to the pathology building of the Third Hospital of Peking University to deliver something, but happened to meet them sorting out some specimens. Many  lung specimen of patients who had been smoking for decades and those diagnosed with lung cancer appeared in front of me, i suddenly felt a little scared and nauseous.Since then, I have made up my mind to discourage my boyfriend from quitting smoking, but after a few years, it still didn’t work. It seems that quitting smoking is a long battle, and only through persistence can people quit smoking.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-13.png"></p><h3 id="Lung-cancer-is-the-largest-cancer-in-the-world"><a href="#Lung-cancer-is-the-largest-cancer-in-the-world" class="headerlink" title="Lung cancer is the largest cancer in the world"></a>Lung cancer is the largest cancer in the world</h3><p><img src="/images/pasted-14.png"></p><p>Let me first talk about why governments all over the world are appealing to quit smoking. After all, as the world’s second largest cancer, lung cancer has led to an increasing number of people to die in the world, which is still increasing year by year. Furthermore, Lung cancer has become the cancer with the highest age-standardized incidence rate (ASIR) and age-standardized mortality rate (ASMR) in the world.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-15.png" alt=" "></p><h3 id="Tobacco-control-is-the-most-important-measure-in-preventing-lung-cancer"><a href="#Tobacco-control-is-the-most-important-measure-in-preventing-lung-cancer" class="headerlink" title="Tobacco control is the most important measure in preventing lung cancer"></a>Tobacco control is the most important measure in preventing lung cancer</h3><p>As is known to all, smoking is the most important factor causing lung cancer, and most of the incidence and death of lung cancer can be attributed to smoking. China is the world’s largest tobacco producer and consumer, and there are more than 300 million smokers in China, 740 million people are harmed by second-hand smoke, and more than 1.2 million people die from smoking and second-hand smoke every year.</p><p>Faced with such terrifying numbers, I hope that when China vigorously calls for quitting smoking, it is like some countries that it can also forcefully require pictures of smoking hazards to be printed on the packaging to give people a warning effect. Regardless of the country, tobacco control is the most important factor in the prevention and control of lung cancer.</p><h3 id="Quitting-smoking-is-definitely-good-but-simultaneously-it-is-really-difficult"><a href="#Quitting-smoking-is-definitely-good-but-simultaneously-it-is-really-difficult" class="headerlink" title="Quitting smoking is definitely good, but simultaneously, it is really difficult"></a>Quitting smoking is definitely good, but simultaneously, it is really difficult</h3><p><img src="/images/pasted-16.png"></p><p>Five tips for quitting smoking:</p><blockquote></blockquote><ol><li>Always remind yourself that smoking is a disease</li><li>Getting rid of nicotine should be compulsive</li><li>Remember that smoking affects everything about you</li><li>Make up your mind before you quit smoking</li><li>Seek help from a doctor or psychologist</li></ol><p><img src="/images/pasted-17.png"></p><p>Based on the experience of my friends, it is very difficult to quit smoking, and a little temptation can easily cause quitters to smoke again. Simultaneously, related studies have shown that quitters will experience weight rebound, cardiovascular disease and increased risk of diabetes in the early stages of quitting smoking. Smokers have to quit smoking for more than 15 years before their lung function recover as a non-smoker. From a long-term perspective, there is no doubt that quitting smoking is beneficial for human health!</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-18.png"></p><p>Even the soldiers in WeChat emojis have successfully quit smoking, don’t wait, for the sake of health, quit smoking right now!</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>February</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>It&#39;s easy to deal with dysmenorrhea</title>
    <link href="/2021/02/02/It-s-easy-to-deal-with-dysmenorrhea/"/>
    <url>/2021/02/02/It-s-easy-to-deal-with-dysmenorrhea/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When I was a child, I loved chasing after and fighting with boys, which made me believe that men and women had the same fighting capacity. Until one day, I began to menstruate, and the severe pain made my fighting capacity smaller and smaller until I became negative. Since then, regular or irregular dysmenorrhea enables me to see the gentle smile of God in the dizziness of pain. While the consciousness of the brain is fuzzy, the pain in the lower abdomen brings the psychedelic mind back to reality.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-6.png"></p><p>The pain also makes me think that menstruation, which makes woman be afraid of both its coming and not coming, is just a bug left by God on women. Most of a woman’s long life is spent playing games with it.</p><p>Actually, dysmenorrhea is very common among women. 50-90% of women suffer from dysmenorrhea. Severe dysmenorrhea is like robbery, which makes people lose the ability to move and seriously affects their daily work, study and life.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-7.png"></p><p>According to statistics of relevant research, 80% of primary dysmenorrhea can be effectively relieved by painkillers. However, due to the stigmatization of painkillers, many women prefer to try various folk prescriptions rather than take painkillers. Many girls can only endure severe pain because they are afraid of the side effects of painkillers.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-8.png"></p><p>This includes me in the past. Until I was in Canada, I went to the pharmacy because of my menstrual pain. The pharmacist explained the principle to me and told me that some painkillers were completely acceptable. After referring to a lot of literature and taking relevant painkillers, I can’t help sighing that painkillers are the light of women!</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-9.png"></p><h3 id="Correct-the-name-for-painkillers"><a href="#Correct-the-name-for-painkillers" class="headerlink" title="Correct the name for painkillers"></a>Correct the name for painkillers</h3><p>A lot of people may be faced with such confusions: some say that painkillers are addictive, some say that they are not addictive. In fact, they may confuse these two kinds of painkillers (narcotic and non narcotic).</p><ol><li>The painkillers with the risk of addiction is opium drugs, which can’t be bought at will and they are prescription drugs and strictly controlled.</li><li>The non steroidal anti-inflammatory drugs eaten during dysmenorrhea has nno risk of addiction.</li></ol><p><img src="/images/pasted-10.png"></p><p>For example, ibuprofen relives the pain through the inhibition of prostaglandin secretion. Compared with opium painkillers, NSAIDs are more like soldiers fighting outside, helping the brain calm down external chaos. They work hard at the front line, and will not make the brain get addicted to it.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-11.png"></p><p>The side effects of taking a few painkillers occasionally are really insignificant compared with severe dysmenorrhea. Moreover, ibuprofen can be hardly detected after 2 days in vivo, and there is no need to worry about the accumulation of toxicity.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-12.png"></p><p>Taking me as an example, I recommend girls suffering from dysmenorrhea to try painkillers bravely, in which Ibuprofen is the priority, because it has both excellent effect and safety. Dysmenorrhea can also be relieved by non drug means, such as abdominal hot compress, non menstrual aerobic exercise, etc. Finally, I wish women all over the world to stay away from dysmenorrhea!</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>February</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Adults&#39; collapse starts with hemorrhoids</title>
    <link href="/2021/01/26/Adults-collapse-starts-with-hemorrhoids/"/>
    <url>/2021/01/26/Adults-collapse-starts-with-hemorrhoids/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I suddenly received a message from my cousin that he was diagnosed with hemorrhoids and was undergoing surgery. He was always wondering why he had hemorrhoids in his butt?  In fact, there are the saying that nine in ten people have hemorrhoids in Chinese folk story. Although the facts are not so exaggerated, due to poor diet and living habits, more people do get hemorrhoids at a young age，therefore, let’s talk about hemorrhoids today.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-0.png"></p><h3 id="What-is-hemorrhoids"><a href="#What-is-hemorrhoids" class="headerlink" title="What is hemorrhoids?"></a>What is hemorrhoids?</h3><p>Hemorrhoids are the most common chronic anorectal disease. There is a structure called anal cushion in the rectum, which is responsible for many fine functions of the anus, including sensation, defecation, etc., similar to the door keeper of the anus. Sitting or standing for a long time will cause the anal cushion to move down, and the blood vessels in the anal cushion will bulge, forming a sick structure, namely, hemorrhoids.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-1.png"></p><p>According to different growing positions, hemorrhoids can be divided into three types, namely，internal hemorrhoids, external hemorrhoids, and mixed hemorrhoids.</p><p>In fact, many hemorrhoids are asymptomatic and won’t make you restless. If there are symptoms, most of them are bleeding after defecation, or prolapse of hemorrhoids in the anus, anal pain, itching and so on.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-2.png"></p><p>Treatment is not needed in asymptomatic hemorrhoids. If there are various discomforts in the anus, patients can try to alleviate the symptom by adjusting the diet, keeping the stool smooth, taking a bath in warm water, and keeping the anus clean. If the symptoms are still not eliminated, patients should see a doctor in time.</p><h3 id="If-you-“unfortunately”-get-hemorrhoids"><a href="#If-you-“unfortunately”-get-hemorrhoids" class="headerlink" title="If you “unfortunately” get hemorrhoids"></a>If you “unfortunately” get hemorrhoids</h3><p>When we have symptoms of hemorrhoids, we must seek medical treatment regardless of face in time. The general principles of treatment depend on the specific conditions of hemorrhoids:</p><ol><li>No symptoms-pay attention to it at usual days, no treatment required.</li><li>Less serious symptoms-conservative treatment is recommended.</li><li>Frequent bleeding, severe prolapse, less effective conservative treatment-surgery is recommended.</li></ol><p><img src="/images/pasted-3.png"></p><p>These five points have to be paid attention to whether you have hemorrhoids or not:</p><blockquote></blockquote><ol><li>Do not sit and stand for a long time. The occurrence of hemorrhoids is related to venous stasis.</li><li>Do not hesitate to go to the toilet</li><li>Eat more fruits and vegetables to ensure taking in adequate fiber</li><li>Clean up regularly</li><li>Carry out levator ani exercises frequently, if necessary, take warm water sitz baths</li></ol><p>If you do not have hemorrhoids, please remember: don’t stand for a long time, don’t squat for too long, eat more fruits and vegetables rich in fiber, and do more exercises.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-4.png"></p><p>Finally, I wish all adults can take care of their bodies and have a healthy butt, so as to stay away from hemorrhoids!</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-5.png"></p><p>We learn another strange knowledge!</p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>January</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Dose the whole family has to check their body once one person is infected with Helicobacter pylori?</title>
    <link href="/2021/01/09/Dose-the-whole-family-has-to-check-their-body-once-one-person-is-infected-with-Helicobacter-pylori/"/>
    <url>/2021/01/09/Dose-the-whole-family-has-to-check-their-body-once-one-person-is-infected-with-Helicobacter-pylori/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Years ago, for a long period of time, my mother always received a lot of calls from friends and relatives, saying that in her physical examination report: HP positive, DOB value ≥ 4, there may be Helicobacter pylori infection, thus it is suggested that she should see a doctor in the digestive department.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-25.png"></p><p>Many people’s question lies in the fact that they heard Helicobacter pylori is not only the cause of a series of gastric diseases (including gastric cancer), but is also highly infectious. It’s of course possible possible for one person to infect the whole family, so should all family members receive treatment?</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-26.png"></p><p>In fact, in modern medicine, people have not made clear of the specific path of Helicobacter pylori infection, and it is generally believed that the main route is fecal-oral, there may also be oral-oral route. (infection is not easy to be caused by kissing, because HP mainly exists in the stomach, and the detection rate in the mouth is very low.)</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-27.png"></p><p>However, family members are the closest people around us, living with us every day, and cross infection is more likely to occur. Relevant evidence has showed that most children are infected with Helicobacter pylori before 10 years old; if the hostess is infected with Helicobacter pylori, the infection rate of their children is often higher. Bad eating habits, no split meals and so on may bring bacteria to family members (especially young children), leading to infection of Helicobacter pylori.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-28.png"></p><p>Based on the current evidence, Helicobacter pylori infection is an important risk factor for intestinal type gastric cancer (the most common gastric cancer type), and the risk can be reduced by timely clearance of infection cases. Helicobacter pylori infection is very common in Chinese people (about 50%). Although adults may not be affected by family infection, there is a high probability that they have been infected with Helicobacter pylori for a long time.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-29.png"></p><p>For our own health, whether families members are infected with Helicobacter pylori or not, they should pay attention to their infection and go to the hospital for check. Even if they are unfortunately infected, after quadruple therapy, the diseasecan be quickly eradicated. (quadruple therapy includes several gastric drugs: gastric acid inhibitor + bismuth agent + two kinds of antibiotics, oral treatment, the course of treatment is recommended to be 10-14 days). Many studies have shown that it is difficult for adults to ne infected again after eradicating Helicobacter pylori.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-30.png"></p><p>Therefore, we don’t worry about this too much，and should develop the habit of split meals with chopsticks and spoon. Simultaneously, wash hands before and after meals can avoid being infected by Helicobacter pylori.</p><p><img src="/images/pasted-31.png"></p>]]></content>
    
    
    
    <tags>
      
      <tag>January</tag>
      
    </tags>
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
